<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Five Thrive</title>
    <description>Modern software development company specializing in Ruby on Rails and Shopify development expertise</description>
    <link>http://fivethrive.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://fivethrive.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 09:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 09:46:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>KISSmetrics integration on Shopify</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-long-of-the-short-of-it-kissmetrics-on-shopify-tldr&quot;&gt;The long of the short of it: KISSmetrics on Shopify (TL;DR)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customer analytics provide the metrics needed to understand who your customers are and how they interact with your business. KISSmetrics is customer analytics at its finest and getting it set up on your Shopify store has never been more complete and simple with our integration app. &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/kissmetrics&quot;&gt;Start understanding your customers today!&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-and-why-do-i-want-kissmetrics-on-shopify&quot;&gt;What is it and why do I want KISSmetrics on Shopify?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KISSmetrics describes iteself this way: “Google Analytics tells you what’s happening. KISSmetrics tells you who’s doing it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plain and simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you struggle to make each sale or you have trouble keeping your products in stock, you should always be trying to learn more to understand your customers. Even failing businesses manage to make a sale or two during the firey decent into obscurity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One major difference you can make to stand out among your competitors, not only on the ever growing Shopify platform but everyone selling everywhere online, is to &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; understand your customers. Not your target market, or your ideal customer but the people that &lt;em&gt;actually visit&lt;/em&gt; and (hopefully) buy from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take your most recent sale, for example. Do you know where that person came from and what marketing effort brought them in? How long has it been between their first visit to your site and when they actually made a purchase? How many times have they visited before purchasing? Are they a repeat buyer? If so, when was the last time they bought? Have they ever returned a product for a refund? How much have they spent with you over time and have they ever left a review? Do you have the data to quickly calculate their customer lifetime value?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those questions aren’t answered with Google analytics alone. KISSmetrics excels at providing all that information in easy to use and very rich reports and unlocks data that can be used to truly grasp who your customers are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-get-kissmetrics-on-shopify&quot;&gt;How to get KISSmetrics on Shopify&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until now, you could either manually integrate your Shopify store with KISSmetrics or hire a developer to do it. This is time consuming, costly, incomplete and requires coding experience. However, what typically costs somewhere between $400 and $700 dollars to have a developer manually integrate can now be done in less than a minute! It also uninstalls cleanly without any extra work! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using this app gives you more time to learn the KISSmetrics product and really evaluate the free trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve removed the hassle of setting up KISSmetrics on Shopify completely! We built an app that gets a Shopify store completely integrated with KISSmetrics by simply adding the API key provided in your KISSMetrics account settings! KISSmetrics offers documentation with &lt;a href=&quot;http://support.kissmetrics.com/best-practices/ecommerce-essentials.html&quot;&gt;best practices&lt;/a&gt; for their ecommerce clients and this app takes care of everything on the list! The guess work around making sure the data is being sent correctly is removed because all of the heavy lifting is already done and validated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you manually integrate, you can’t get refund or cancellation data! In short, you, a Shopify merchant, can now track each customer’s behavior from initial visit to return visit to purchase and even returns by simply copy-pasting an API Key!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get started truly understanding your customers! &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/kissmetrics&quot;&gt;Install the 14 Day Free Trial Now!&lt;/a&gt; and become your customers’ best friend!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://fivethrive.com/blog/2014/08/21/integrate-kissmetrics-on-shopify/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://fivethrive.com/blog/2014/08/21/integrate-kissmetrics-on-shopify/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
