<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Five Thrive</title>
    <description>Shopify Partner Phoenix | Software Development Phoenix | Ruby on Rails Phoenix | Modern software development company specializing in Ruby on Rails and Shopify development expertise</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 21:41:14 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 21:41:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Façadify EOL</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;faadify-reaches-the-end-of-its-life&quot;&gt;Façadify reaches the end of its life&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facadify started out as a joint venture to make it super simple to integrate Google Content Experiments on a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; storefront. This, like many adventures, went very well in the beginning. It helped many people but not nearly as many as we’d hoped. Then, other projects came along, took priority and eventually Façadify fell into disrepair. Unfortunately, Façadify never did quite fully meet the needs of the customers and therefore, we decided to decommission the integration and amicably part ways on the venture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is enough interest, perhaps someday we will take the lessons we learned with Façadify and build out something to meet the need of A/B testing a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; store.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/2015/02/10/shutting-down-facadify/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/2015/02/10/shutting-down-facadify/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shopify integrations</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-we-build-integrations-for-shopify&quot;&gt;Why we build integrations for Shopify&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a merchant selling online, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; is our favorite platform by far. In fact, we love it so much we’ve built a number of integration applications to help merchants increase their conversion rate. You may have noticed from our home page that we have primarily integrated with analytics platforms. “Why,” you might ask, “can’t those integrations be done without your apps?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, sure. If you’re a highly technical person. We tell people who have development teams that they do not need to use our integrations all the time. The thing is, we didn’t make the integrations to help those people who can and want to manually integrate with theses services. We built them for the merchant who wants to focus on honing their store’s usability, the layout, the marketing copy. We built them so you, the merchant, can focus on your product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re passionate about your product, you probably don’t want to spend time messing around with theme files, javascript tags and validating that your integration data is being tracked properly. That’s where we come in. We’ve integrated with the services we have found to provide some of the most useful information in helping improve conversion rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;kissmetrics&quot;&gt;KISSmetrics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customer analytics provide the metrics needed to understand who your customers are and how they interact with your business. KISSmetrics is customer analytics at its finest and getting it set up on your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; store has never been more complete and simple with our integration app. Plus, when you’re done, it removes cleanly from your shop upon uninstallation! &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/kissmetrics?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Start understanding your customers today&lt;/a&gt; or read more about it &lt;a href=&quot;http://fivethrive.com/blog/2014/08/21/integrate-kissmetrics-on-shopify/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;crazyegg&quot;&gt;CrazyEgg&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heatmaps give clear and compelling information about how your user interacts with your storefront. CrazyEgg and KISSmetrics were both founded by Neil Patel so it made sense to provide integrations for both. &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/crazyegg?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Get CrazyEgg tracking your customers!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;navilytics&quot;&gt;Navilytics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not just another heatmap tool, we are really impressed by this one! Full discloser: we are affiliates of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.navilytics.com/?r=1476&quot;&gt;Navilytics&lt;/a&gt; but because we believe in them so much we are willing to put our name behind a recommendation. They offer a free tier so you can try them out today at no cost! We give you 14 days to try our integration for free too so what are you waiting for, &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/navilytics?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;watch recordings of your customers interacting with your shop today&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure there will be more as we continue to work with shops all over the world looking for easier integration with other services. Feel free to contact us if you would like us to integrate a service for you too!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/2015/02/01/shopify-integrations/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/2015/02/01/shopify-integrations/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KISSmetrics integration on Shopify</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-long-of-the-short-of-it-kissmetrics-on-shopify-tldr&quot;&gt;The long of the short of it: KISSmetrics on Shopify (TL;DR)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customer analytics provide the metrics needed to understand who your customers are and how they interact with your business. KISSmetrics is customer analytics at its finest and getting it set up on your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; store has never been more complete and simple with our integration app. &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/kissmetrics&quot;&gt;Start understanding your customers today!&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-it-and-why-do-i-want-kissmetrics-on-shopify&quot;&gt;What is it and why do I want KISSmetrics on Shopify?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KISSmetrics describes iteself this way: “Google Analytics tells you what’s happening. KISSmetrics tells you who’s doing it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plain and simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you struggle to make each sale or you have trouble keeping your products in stock, you should always be trying to learn more to understand your customers. Even failing businesses manage to make a sale or two during the firey decent into obscurity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One major difference you can make to stand out among your competitors, not only on the ever growing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; platform but everyone selling everywhere online, is to &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; understand your customers. Not your target market, or your ideal customer but the people that &lt;em&gt;actually visit&lt;/em&gt; and (hopefully) buy from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take your most recent sale, for example. Do you know where that person came from and what marketing effort brought them in? How long has it been between their first visit to your site and when they actually made a purchase? How many times have they visited before purchasing? Are they a repeat buyer? If so, when was the last time they bought? Have they ever returned a product for a refund? How much have they spent with you over time and have they ever left a review? Do you have the data to quickly calculate their customer lifetime value?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those questions aren’t answered with Google analytics alone. KISSmetrics excels at providing all that information in easy to use and very rich reports and unlocks data that can be used to truly grasp who your customers are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-get-kissmetrics-on-shopify&quot;&gt;How to get KISSmetrics on Shopify&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until now, you could either manually integrate your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; store with KISSmetrics or hire a developer to do it. This is time consuming, costly, incomplete and requires coding experience. However, what typically costs somewhere between $400 and $700 dollars to have a developer manually integrate can now be done in less than a minute! It also uninstalls cleanly without any extra work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using this app gives you more time to learn the KISSmetrics product and really evaluate the free trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve removed the hassle of setting up KISSmetrics on Shopify completely! We built an app that gets a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; store completely integrated with KISSmetrics by simply adding the API key provided in your KISSMetrics account settings! KISSmetrics offers documentation with &lt;a href=&quot;http://support.kissmetrics.com/best-practices/ecommerce-essentials.html&quot;&gt;best practices&lt;/a&gt; for their ecommerce clients and this app takes care of everything on the list! The guess work around making sure the data is being sent correctly is removed because all of the heavy lifting is already done and validated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you manually integrate, you can’t get refund or cancellation data! In short, you, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopify.com/?ref=fivethrive&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; merchant, can now track each customer’s behavior from initial visit to return visit to purchase and even returns by simply copy-pasting an API Key!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get started truly understanding your customers! &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.shopify.com/kissmetrics&quot;&gt;Install the 14 Day Free Trial Now!&lt;/a&gt; and become your customers’ best friend!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/2014/08/21/integrate-kissmetrics-on-shopify/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/2014/08/21/integrate-kissmetrics-on-shopify/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
